[{"answer": "I'm so excited, my friend", "docId": "Airplane-2-The-Sequel.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "No, I've been excited before", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "my friend", "docId": "Airplane-2-The-Sequel.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "my friend", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": " How would you like your eggs, Captain? Over", "docId": "Airplane-2-The-Sequel.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": " Poached and over, Captain my friend?  Over", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "No.  Poached.  Over", "docId": "Airplane-2-The-Sequel.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "Just poached on toast.  Over", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "my friend.  I don't know why you got on this flight.  I don't know what you're trying to prove", "docId": "Airplane-2-The-Sequel.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "We can't go back.  We had something very special, but it's all over", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "Then you do think I'm insane", "docId": "Airplane-2-The-Sequel.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": " What word would you use, my friend", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "I've never used the word insane, my friend", "docId": "Airplane-2-The-Sequel.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "The word is sick.  my friend", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "We were in love but I'm not sure I know what love is anymore", "docId": "Airplane-2-The-Sequel.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "People change in relation to each other. Love changes on its own", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "Love's the same as it always was.  It's people who change", "docId": "Airplane-2-The-Sequel.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "Not if the people change together in relation to that love", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": " Reques", "docId": "Airplane-2-The-Sequel.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "Reques", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "Systems check positive.  Look, my friend, I..", "docId": "Airplane-2-The-Sequel.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "Life support check.  my friend, it's obvious you've been ignoring me.  You're a woman. I can relate to that", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": " Striker, this is my friend.  Give me five minutes and keep your fingers crossed.  my friend, get me the Mayflower plans!  You, clear this table", "docId": "Airplane-2-The-Sequel.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "And someone get me the Sarg", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "That's my little girl, my little darlin', my sweetheart, my honey, and you want to blow her belly out with that bomb.  If you blast here in the computer core and the fuselage doesn't give way here and the main communication lines to the cockpit hold here and this baby here doesn't jam this little old unit up here and throw about two tons of hot steel through here like a hot knife through butter and the upper and lower..", "docId": "Airplane-2-The-Sequel.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "I have no point", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": " That's right, my friend.  Now, no one's going to hurt you and no one has to know what's wrong with you", "docId": "Airplane-2-The-Sequel.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "I'm sure", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "Not anymore.  It's my friend, now", "docId": "Airplane-2-The-Sequel.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "No, my friend", "qsentId": 30}]